Guide to the Judy Blume Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 2017 Acquisition, 1952-2017; 117.75; (125 boxes) + 1 roll
  - Key West Material, 1961-2015; 99.62; (106 boxes)
    - In the unlikely event, notes, undated (Box 50)
    - In the unlikely event, "part 2, November 2011 draft", 2011 November (Box 50)
    - In the unlikely event, "second draft Nov Dec 2012 and Jan.", 2 folders (Box 50)
    - In the unlikely event, draft, undated; 3 folders (Box 50)
    - In the unlikely event, research and notes, 2004, undated (Box 50)
    - In the unlikley event, research files, 1952–2015; 9 folders (Box 51)
    - In the unlikely event, "verifications - per copy", undated (Box 51)
    - In the unlikely event, "extra part 1&2 June 4, 2012 to NY", 2011 (Box 51)
    - In the unlikley event, "from part two June 4, 2012 to NY", undated (Box 51)
    - In the unlikley event, "stuff from earlier drafts June 4, 2012 to NY", undated (Box 51)
    - Las Vegas High School 1955 yearbook (Box 51)
    - In the unlikely event, "summer/fall revisions with Carole Baron notes (JB notes) Nov. 2014", 2014 November; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - In the unlikely event, "older version Joanne A=B (to Santa Fe)", undated; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - In the unlikely event, part 3, undated (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, "extra stuff from part three June 4, 2012 to NY misc. notes", 2013-2014, undated (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, "old notes and early pages", 2012, undated (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, "notes and early pages", undated (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, outline, undated (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, miscellaneous drafts and notes, undated (Box 52)
    - Article, 2014 September 21 (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, research material, 1952, 2014 (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, research and drafts, 2014, undated (Box 52)
    - Correspondence about Banned Books Weeks, 2014 (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, "notes for book. Carole meetings 2014 June" (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, Part 2 correspondence, 2014 October (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, Part 2, "working October 2014 revision draft", 2014 October (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, notes and drafts, 2014, undated (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, "working summer/Fall 2014 revisions", 2014–2015 (Box 52)
    - In the unlikely event, "pre-final draft 11/15/2014", 3 folders (Box 52)
    - In the unlikley event, "second draft Nov Dec 2012 and Jan", undated; 3 folders (Box 53)
    - In the unlikely event, draft, undated; 4 folders (Box 53)
    - In the unlikely event, proof, 2015 February; 4 folders (Box 53)
    - In the unlikely event, proof, 2015 March; 4 folders (Box 53)
    - In the unlikley event, "working summer 2014 revision draft", 2 folders (Box 53)
    - In the unlikely event, "working summer 2014 revision draft as sent to Claude", 3 folders (Box 53)
    - In the unlikely event, "current draft (May 2014) Parts 1-3 2014 The drafts for Joanne's first changes", 3 folders (Box 54)
    - In the unlikely event, "last revision typed and entered by Joanne before current - May 22,2014", 3 folders (Box 54)
    - In the unlikely event, draft, undated; 4 folders (Box 54)
    - In the unlikely event, "working November 2014 final revisions", 2014 November; 4 folders (Box 54)
    - In the unlikely event, "Judy's 2009 plane project", 2009-2011, undated; 2 folders (Box 55)
    - In the unlikely event, draft and "instructions in case of Judy's death", 2014; 4 folders (Box 55)
    - In the unlikely event, "Part Two/2nd draft ready for next draft/KW winter 2013", 2 folders (Box 55)
    - In the unlikley event, "final Key West draft missing Mike Monsky, 1987/prologue, 1987/ending", undated; 4 folders (Box 55)
    - In the unlikely event, "working November 2014 final revisions", 2 folders (Box 55)
    - In the unlikely event, "first draft Parts 1-2 parts of 3 (copy) printed June, 2012", 2012 June; 3 folders (Box 55)
    - In the unlikely event, "untitled MS by author known to Suzanne Gluck", 2014 May; 4 folders (Box 55)
    - In the unlikely event, page proofs, undated; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - In the unlikely event, "3rd page proofs", 2015; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - In the unlikely event, "2nd page proofs? Copy of proofs?", undated; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - In the unlikely event, page proofs, Feb. 2015, 2015 February; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - In the unlikely event, page proofs, third pass with corrections, to Kristen, 2015 March; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - Cool zone with The pain & the great one, drafts and proofs, 2007, undated; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Soupy Saturdays with The pain & the great one, drafts and proofs, 2006-2007, undated; 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Going, going, gone! with The pain & the great one, proofs and drafts, 2007, undated; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Soupy Saturdays with The pain & the great one, "Promo", 2007, undated (Box 57)
    - "Art - Pain & Great One", undated (Box 57)
    - Soupy Saturdays with The pain & the great one, " drafts Mr. Soupy Oct '06", undated (Box 57)
    - "P & GO overall art", undated (Box 57)
    - "Pain and the Great One general notes", 2006, undated (Box 57)
    - Pain & the great one, "Only white food", undated (Box 57)
    - Soupy Saturdays with The pain & the great one, miscellaneous material, 2004-2006, undated; 8 folders (Box 57)
    - Cool zone with The pain & the great one, miscellaneous material, 2006-2007, undated; 4 folders (Box 57)
    - Going, going, gone! with The pain & the great one, miscellaenous material, 2005-2007, undated; 6 folders (Box 57)
    - Going, going, gone! with The pain & the great one, drafts, 2007, undated (Box 59)
    - Friend or fiend? with The pain & the great one, miscellaneous material, 2005-2008, undated; 8 folders (Box 59)
    - "JB wrote / 17 essay / 07", undated (Box 59)
    - Going, going, gone! with The pain & the great one, The furry booger drafts, 2007, undated (Box 59)
    - Soupy Saturdays with The pain & the great one, notes and art, 2007, undated (Box 59)
    - Cool zone with The pain & the great one, proofs, 2007 (Box 58)
    - Cool zone with The pain & the great one, miscelleanous material, 2004-2007, undated; 8 folders (Box 59)
    - "Book #3 Pain & great one series Summer '07, Book #4 Friend or fiend Winter '08 sent to Bev. Horowitz June 27, 2008 Revised", 2007-2008, undated; 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Cool zone with The pain & the great one, miscellaneous materials, 2006-2007, undated; 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Cool zone with The pain & the great one, notes and drafts, 2004, undated (Box 60)
    - Double Fudge, drafts, 2002, undated; 3 folders (Box 60)
    - Double Fudge, notes, undated (Box 60)
    - " Fudge book updates '02", 2002, undated (Box 60)
    - Double Fudge, 2001; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Tiger eyes, notes, 2011, undated (Box 60)
    - Tiger eyes, script, drafts, 2009-2010, undated; 9 folders (Box 60)
    - Tiger eyes, script, drafts, 2009-2010, undated; 4 folders (Box 61)
    - Tiger eyes, "Judy's most important notes 2010", 2010, undated (Box 61)
    - "Cover art reissues 2004", 2004-2005, undated (Box 61)
    - "Proposed re-released of Random House books cover art", undated (Box 61)
    - "Cover art - Fudge Spring 2007", 2006, undated (Box 61)
    - "Cover art - Forever Spring 2007", 2006, undated (Box 61)
    - Cover art, 2003, undated; 4 folders (Box 61)
    - "Judy Blume - LL Version A - icons/photos", undated (Box 61)
    - UK cover art…, 2008, undated (Box 61)
    - Forever, proofs, Pulse Teen Edition, 2007 (Box 58)
    - Fan photos, undated (Box 61)
    - Fan photos, undated (Box 62)
    - "SCWBI party" material, 1994-1998, undated; 3 folders (Box 63)
    - "Power lunch - Citymeals-on-Wheels - November 14, 1994", 1997–1998 (Box 63)
    - "Leanna Katz - memorial May 1, 1997" (Box 63)
    - "NCAC" material, 1994-1997, undated; 4 folders (Box 63)
    - "SCWBI conference August, 1996", 1995 November 4 (Box 63)
    - "Hungry Mind Review/Fall '91", 1983-1991, undated (Box 63)
    - "Urgent business", 1990-1991, undated (Box 63)
    - "Op Ed piece on censorship", 1995-1997, undated (Box 63)
    - "Celebrity Focus - Sheila Casserly", 1998 April 12 (Box 63)
    - Miscelleanous materials related to writing, 1990, undated (Box 63)
    - "General interest", 1970-1994, undated (Box 63)
    - "Articles: abuse", 1981-1990, undated (Box 63)
    - "Stepfamily information", 1982-1985, undated (Box 63)
    - Summer sisters, publicity tour, 1998 (Box 63)
    - "Norma's articles & interviews", undated (Box 63)
    - "Interview requests Jan. - May 1998", 1997–1998 (Box 63)
    - "Contributions - '98", 1998 (Box 63)
    - "Other business", 1998 March 31 (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous material removed from books, 1998, undated (Box 63)
    - "Fall/Winter events, accepted 98-99", 1998 (Box 63)
    - "Fall 98 -invitations, social events, fundraisers, etc", 1998-1999, undated (Box 63)
    - "E-mail", 1998–1999 (Box 63)
    - "Fall 98 auction requests", 1998, undated (Box 63)
    - "Milwaukee tales with pix", 1991, undated (Box 63)
    - "Pub tours to return to NYC", 1993, undated (Box 63)
    - "Publicity tour: Fudge-a-mania October/Nov 1990", 1990, undated (Box 63)
    - "Elwood", 1996, undated (Box 63)
    - "Recipes", 1981-1990, undated (Box 63)
    - "Interview with Nyla", 1992, undated (Box 63)
    - Here's to you, Rachel Robinson, "marketing ideas - JB/Dell", 1994, undated (Box 63)
    - Here's to you, Rachel Robinson, "publicity", 1993-1998, undated (Box 63)
    - "Toronto - November 13-15, 1993 publicity tour", 1993, undated (Box 63)
    - "Talk to Your Kids About Sex campaign", undated (Box 63)
    - "MVY Public Library", 1998 February 26 (Box 63)
    - "Gale, Kathy Johnson", 1991-1994, undated (Box 63)
    - "First edition", 1984-1994, undated (Box 63)
    - "Language", 1994-1998, undated (Box 63)
    - "Requests - JB to speak Fall 98", 1997–1998 (Box 63)
    - Illustrated shoes, undated (Box 64)
    - "Corres: Dick Jackson 95-98", 1995-1999, undated (Box 65)
    - "Personal correspondence 2012 authors", 1968-2017, undated (Box 65)
    - "Corresp/personal/1984-1985", 1984-1985, undated (Box 65)
    - "Corerspondence/editors - 1984-1985", 1983-1999, udnated (Box 65)
    - "Dillon Press biography (correspondence, etc.)", 1980–1982 (Box 65)
    - "Personal correspondence 2003", 2002-2003, undated (Box 65)
    - "Personal correspondence 2005", 2002-2005, udnated (Box 65)
    - "Trumpet Club - school visit Tuesday, March 10, 1992", 1991-1993, undated (Box 65)
    - "Betsy Tacy Society", 1992-1993, undated (Box 65)
    - "Pen Faulkner", undated (Box 65)
    - "Pinto, Sara", 1996 (Box 65)
    - "Parties", 1987, undated (Box 65)
    - "Parties: lists and info", 1982-1989, undated (Box 65)
    - "Margaret's 20th birthday party December 4, 1990", 1990, undated (Box 65)
    - " Fudge Party '02", 2002, undated (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1996–2008 (Box 65)
    - Are you there God? It's me, Margaret, fan book, 2008 (Box 65)
    - Tales of fourth grade nothing and Superfudge, fan book, 1990 (Box 65)
    - Promotional materials related to novels, undated (Box 65)
    - Kids fund notes, undated; 3 folders (Box 66)
    - Tiger eyes banner, undated (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "final draft demo 7" and notes, 2006, undated; 3 folders (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "screenplay 1988", 1988 January 4 (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "4/09/07 as sent to Larry, Jane & Erin", 2007, undated (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "screenplay correspond. May '06 and earlier", 2006, undated; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Deenie, screenplay and outlines, 2006, undated; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "Disney movie correspondence", 2006, undated (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "May 05 JB & LAB revised Pam's screenplay", 2005-2006, undated; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "Erin's outline June 23, 06", 2006 (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "Erin's draft 2/07", 2007 (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "Judy's revisions to Erin's draft 2/07", 2007 February (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "As sent to Larry 2/22/07", 2007 February 22 (Box 66)
    - Deenie, "3/12/07 As sent to Larry, Jane & Erin", 2007 March 12 (Box 66)
    - The pain & the great one, promotional material, undated; 3 folders (Box 67)
    - Copies of manuscript material by Judy Blume, 2008, undated; 4 folders (Box 67)
    - New Zealand scrapbook, 1989 (Box 67)
    - Integrating the literature of Judy Blume in the classroom, 1990 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1997-2000, undated (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1992, undated (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 106)
    - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 126)
    - Alphabet book to Judy from 4th graders, 1995 (Box 67)
    - Knitted uterus, undated (Box 68)
    - Illustrated rock celebrating 30th anniversary of Fudge, 2002 November (Box 68)
    - Photographs, undated; 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Honorary degree from Kean College of New Jersey, 1987 June 5; 2 folders (Box 67)
    - In the unlikely event, proof, 2015 June 02 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous material removed from books, 1972-1999, undated; 22 folders (Box 67)
    - Growing up and liking it, 1972 (Box 67)
    - Promotional materials related to novels, undated (Box 69)
    - Awards, 1978–2008 (Box 70)
    - Awards, 1975–2013 (Box 71)
    - Awards, 1961-2010, undated; 12 folders (Box 72)
    - American Academy of Achievement Golden Plate award, 1994 June 18 (Box 73)
    - Louisianna Association of School Librarians, Best Book award, 1982 (Box 74)
    - Awards, undated; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Jeremiah Ludington Memorial Award, 1983 June 14 (Box 76)
    - Buckeye Children's Book Award, 1982 (Box 77)
    - The Sequoyah Children's Book Award, 1975 April 12 (Box 78)
    - Buckeye Children's Book Award, 1983 (Box 79)
    - Georgia Children's Book Award, 1983 May 7 (Box 80)
    - Georgia Children's Book Award, 1977 May 7 (Box 81)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Humanities Award, State of Isreal Bonds, 1984 January 22 (Box 82)
    - Buckeye Children's Book Award, 2005 (Box 83)
    - The Assembly on Literature for Adolescents of the NCTE Alan Award, 2013 (Box 84)
    - Awards, 1985, undated (Box 85)
    - Awards, 1984, undated (Box 86)
    - Awards, undated (Box 87)
    - One Million Copies sold of SuperFudge, 1981 October (Box 88)
    - Awards, 1977-1983, undated (Box 89)
    - The Milner Award, 1983 (Box 90)
    - National Mother's Day Committee, Outstanding Mother Award, 1982 April 20 (Box 91)
    - Audiovisual Material
      Boxes 6 and 92-103 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Video Material
        - "Harper's great [Ad?]", 1991; 1.0 (Box 6)
        - "Harper house party", 1990 October 28; 1.0 (Box 6)
        - "Judy Blume presentation to Penguin Publishing…", undated; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "Healthy kids show #10", undated; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "Literature to enjoy & write about…", undated; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "Sheila ABC weekend spec. 3/23/91 12:30 p.m.", 1991 March 23; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "Sheila ABC weekend", undated; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - " Fudge-A-Mania tour September 1990…", 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "Judy Blume Satellite Press tour history tape #1", undated; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "Continental Bookshelf National Book Foundation", undated; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "KTV Carly Simon segment", undated; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "Congratulations to Dave from Judy Blume…", 2002 March 11; 1.0 (Box 92)
        - "Ernie Anastos segment…", 1.0 (Box 93)
        - "K-TV show", undated; 1.0 (Box 93)
        - "Cheerios Literacy Program SMT B-roll", undated; 1.0 (Box 93)
        - "Walden Books", undated; 1.0 (Box 93)
        - " Forever the movie 1976", 1.0 (Box 93)
        - " Fudge-a-Mania thank-you", 1990; 1.0 (Box 93)
        - "Nick news show #49 30 minutes 11/20/95", 1995 November 20; 1.0 (Box 93)
        - "Cuckoo's 66", undated; 1.0 (Box 93)
        - "Petrie in prime dub Bimbener, Zillen, Kinsella", undated; 1.0 (Box 93)
        - "1990-7: George Sailing on Sally J - tape 2012-43", undated; 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "The Key West picture show", undated; 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "1969-1972: Amanda's childhood", 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "Satellite Press tour history tape #2", undated; 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "News for kids", 1993 October 9; 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "Lucky Duck Nick news show #49 adoption TRT: 28:26", undated; 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "1991: Scholastic Book magic - tape 2012-38", 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "1992: Share the excitement - tape 2012-39", 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "2002-2-25: Presenting at the KW literary seminar - tape 2012-40", 2002 February 25; 1.0 (Box 94)
        - "1984/1985: Assorted interviews Smart women tour - tape 2012-21", 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1993-12-3: World News Tonight - tape 2012-20", 1993 December 12; 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1987-3-16: Northwest Afternoon - tape 2012-19", 1987 March 16; 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1984-3-16: Freeman Reports & Crossfire - tape 2012-18", 1984 March 16; 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1991: Dell Books promo - tape 2012-23", 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1996-11-27: Blue Peter, BBC - tape 2012-30", 1996 November 27; 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1998, May & June: Summer sisters tour/assorted interviews - tape 2012-17", 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1987-5-20: IMHI remarks - 2012-31", 1987 May 20; 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1979-6-24: The Tom Snyder Show and Hot Hero Sandwich - tape 2011", 1976 June 24; 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1990-10-12: CBS Home with Judy Blume - tape 2011-8", 1990 October 12; 1.0 (Box 95)
        - "1996-2-27: Good Morning Amer. - tape 2011-13", 1996 February 27; 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "1987-3: Good Morning America - tape 2011-16", 1987 March; 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "1984 Late Night America - tape 2012-37", 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "2003-12-8: Judy/Larry interview, Sheila DVD extra - tape 2012-35", 2003 December 8; 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "People are talking - tape 2012-29", undated; 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "KTCA Arts on 2 - tape 2012-29", undated; 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "1993-11-30: Where in the world is Carmen Sandiego? - tape 2012-26", 1993 November 30; 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "1982 & 1990 Good Morning America discussing censorship/parent-kid...", 1.0 (Box 96)
        - " Fudge-a-mania award thank you - tape 2011-5", undated; 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "2002: Double Fudge tour, 5 interviews - tape 2011-4", 1.0 (Box 96)
        - "1998-06-04: Am Northwest - tape 2011-3", 1998 June 4; 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "1995-01-06: Good Morning America - tape 2011-2", 1995 January 6; 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "1994-05-04: Charlie Rose - tape 2011-1", 1994 May 4; 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "1999-5-7: WTHR noon news Indianapolis - tape 2012-25", 1997 May 7; 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "1998: Canada AM - tape 2011-14", 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "1982: Superfudge book award - tape 2011-12", 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "1990-10: The Joan Rivers Show & CNN Sonya Live - tape 2011-10", 1990 October; 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "1998-5-13: Pamela Wallin - CBC Newsworld - tape 2011-9", 1998 May 13; 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "KTV - tape 2011-7", undated; 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "TLC on the inside - tape 2011-6", undated; 1.0 (Box 97)
        - "Sept. 1980 - Judy's Today Show & Letterman show", 1980 September; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "Detroit media tour - 2-10-84…", 1984 February 10; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "JB Larry King show Apr. 1980", 1980 April; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "Tom Cottle (Jan. 1983)", 1983 January; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "Crossfire (CNN) 11/23/84", 1984 November 23; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "1991-8-12: Planned Parenthood spots - tape 2012-34", 1991 August 12; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "1997-11-20: Rosie O'Donnell Show - tape 2011-15", 1997 November 20; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "1993-10: KCLA the Morning show - tape 2012-22", 1993 October; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "1993-11-15 Petrie in Prime - tape 2012-28", 1993 November 15; 1.0 (Box 98)
        - "Hearst / ABC Judy Blume segment 3/30/80", 1980 March 30; 1.0 (Box 99)
        - "2004 Glamour Women of the Year Judy Blume feature", 1.0 (Box 99)
        - "Battin graduate & author Judy Blume visit Battin Middle School…", 2004 November 19; 1.0 (Box 99)
        - " Forever ", undated; 1.0 (Box 99)
        - "The Open Mind Guest: Judy Blume…", 2000 October 20; 1.0 (Box 99)
        - "Salisbury news clip 12/18/09 (GC re-enactment)", 2009 December 18; 1.0 (Box 99)
        - "3/9/85 Regis Philbin with Judy Blume…", 1985 March 9; 1.0 (Box 99)
        - "National Book Foundation conversation Young at Heart, Brown with Blume", 2004 December 13; 1.0 (Box 99)
        - "National Book Awards CSPAN -2…", 2004 November 21; 1.0 (Box 99)
        - "Judy Blume 7 News (Denver) May 27, 1998, CBS Sunday Morning September 27, 1998", 1.0 (Box 99)
        - " Double Fudge interviews Penguin Putnam Books for Young Readers", undated; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - "Judy Blume on the Late Show starring Joan Rivers March 25, 1987", 1987 March 25; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - "Lost 3-22-06", 2006 March 22; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - "Tell it like it is!", undated; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - "South Park #316 Are you there God? It's me, Jesus", undated; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - "Calico Films Judy Blume Freckle juice ", undated; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - Unidentified, undated; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - "Amanda & Jim's wedding reception w/ Gary and the Wombats 12/28/00", 2000 December 28; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - " Fudge-a-mania thank-you", undated; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - "Scrubs 'My sacrificial clam'", undated; 1.0 (Box 100)
        - "Dutton Publishing Judy Blume Superfudge book award thanks…", 1982 April 13; 1.0 (Box 101)
        - "Kup's Show, Judy Blume, Andrew Greeley Jeff Lyon, Dr. Spock", 1985 March 8; 1.0 (Box 101)
        - "'People are talking' - Judy Blume 3/12/85", 1985 March 12; 1.0 (Box 101)
        - Otherwise known as Sheila the great, 2008; 1 (Box 101)
        - Tiger eyes, 2012; 1 (Box 101)
        - "Personal tapes & shows w/ Judy", undated; 1.0 (Box 102)
        - "Cheerios literacy program SMT B-roll", undated; 1.0 (Box 102)
        - "Judy Blume presentation Penguin Putnam sales meeting…", 2002 April; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - " Superfudge 1982, Fudge-a-mania 1990, Double Fudge 2002", 1982–2002; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "JB TV stuff 2/2 master", 1998–2002; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "JB P+W thanks", undated; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "JB TV stuff 1/2 master", undated; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "Judy Blume Sept. 9, 2004 MV to JR", 2004 September 9; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "2004 tr[opic?] interview", 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "Dinner toasts Cooper/Noel #1", undated; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "Ceremony/reception", undated; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "Vol party 2014 La Pierre open heavenly gospel 10th ann #1", 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "Cooper - Shield rehersal pre-construction play reading", undated; 1.0 (Box 103)
        - "Judy at KW lib. Feb/02", 2002 February (Box 103)
        - Unlabeled Maxell mini DV 60 min, undated; 1.0 (Box 103)
      - Audio Material
        - "Judy Blume", undated; 1 (Box 103)
        - "Judy Blume OP.B. Golden Hours...", undated; 1 (Box 103)
        - "The Trumpet Club, Authors on Tape, Judy Blume", 1991; 1 (Box 103)
        - "NPR, Talk of the Nation, Judy Blume", 1998 October 28; 1 (Box 103)
    - Electronic media, 2002-2011, undated; 20 (Box 104)
      Box 104 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Electronic media, 2011-2015, undated; 9 (Box 105)
      Box 105 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Glenn Horowitz Bookseller Office Material, 1956-2001; 11.5; (11 boxes)